ORIT LESHEM

755 Dunboyne Cres' | London, ON | N5X 1X9 | 519-933-0408 | azmono@gmail.com Portfolio: Orit Leshem

Profile

A self-motivated, goal-oriented full-stack developer specializing in JavaScript, Node.js and React.js.

I have an MBA as well as a Software Engineering Immersive certification and Coding Academy Israel full-stack developer diploma; I am bilingual in English and Hebrew

Core Skills/Competencies

- JavaScript
- Html
- CSS
- React.js
- Node.js
- Angular

- Vue.js
- Python
- Django
- Mongoose
- MongoDB
- PostgreSQL

- ASW S3
- jQuery
- GitHub
- Management
- Problem-Solving
- Flexibility and Innovation

Relevant Work Experience

Full-Stack Developer Fellow

Coding Academy, Tel-Aviv, Israel

April 2021 – June 2021

- Used React.js, Node.js and MongoDB to develop full-stack applications
- Collaborated with team members to develop applications from planning to execution
- Demonstrated efficient performance while inspiring team members to meet expectations

Software Engineering Fellow

April 2021 – June 2021

General Assembly, Toronto, Canada

- Used React.js, Node.js and MongoDB to develop full-stack applications
- Worked with the team on all aspects of application development, from start to finish
- Performed efficiently and motivated team members to achieve team goals

Work Experience

Front Desk Supervisor

September 2021 – September 2022

Idlewyld Inn & Spa, London, Canada

- Demonstrated exceptional customer service skills by effectively managing and resolving quest complaints, increasing customer satisfaction ratings.
- Implemented effective communication, resulting in improved customer service delivery.
- Utilized strong sales skills to upsell hotel services and amenities successfully

ORIT LESHEM

755 Dunboyne Cres' | London, ON | N5X 1X9 | 519-933-0408 | azmono@gmail.com Portfolio: Orit Leshem

General Manager

January 2018 - January 2021

Kinneret-mall shopping center, Jordan Valley, Israel

- Created and executed sales strategy raising appraisal value by 14.7% over two years
- Transformed inner layout by 10% to accommodate two new Mega-retail stores
- Managed 40 properties to provide a first-class rate shopping experience
- Collaborated with the local municipality to provide catering solutions for 500 employees

Business consultant / Business development manager

2014 - 2018

Freelance, Tel-Aviv, Israel

- Co-Founded an Israeli Cyber services company, launched within 3 months of Founding
- Established and managed a Sales and services call center for Afikim Electric vehicles
- Built and trained sales and support teams and set up the IT service infrastructure
- Consulted on HR management and sales training programs for small and medium privately held businesses

Education

2023 2021 2007 2004
2007
2007
2004
2004
2004
arketing
arketing
arketing
ai netilig
2007
2004
J

Emergency Medical Responder (EMR) and Ambulance driver Magen David Adom (Israeli Red Cross first aid organization)

2016 - 2021